{
    "subject": "resource/The_Prometheus_Deception",
    "predicate": "ontology/author",
    "object": "resource/Robert_Ludlum",
    "human_readable": "The author of 'The Prometheus Deception' is Robert Ludlum.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.988500714302063,
            "question": "Is Robert Ludlum the author of 'The Prometheus Deception'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9082838296890259,
            "question": "Who wrote the book 'The Prometheus Deception'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8935117125511169,
            "question": "What is the name of the author who wrote 'The Prometheus Deception'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7978943586349487,
            "question": "Who wrote a thriller called 'The Prometheus Deception'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7819104194641113,
            "question": "Is there a book named 'The Prometheus Deception'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7721388936042786,
            "question": "What is the title of a novel written by Robert Ludlum?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7309709787368774,
            "question": "What book did Robert Ludlum write?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5892673134803772,
            "question": "Can you name a book by Robert Ludlum?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5594310164451599,
            "question": "Robert Ludlum is known for writing which type of books?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3184904456138611,
            "question": "What genre does 'The Prometheus Deception' belong to?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The author of 'The Prometheus Deception' is Robert Ludlum.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7238_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Robert Ludlum is known for writing which type of books?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7238_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a book by Robert Ludlum?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7238_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What book did Robert Ludlum write?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7238_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7238_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7238_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7238_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7238_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7238_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7238_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7238_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7238_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7238_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7238_56.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis response indicates that the information provided in the documents supports the statement that Robert Ludlum is the author of 'The Prometheus Deception'."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}